<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ExtJS on Anthony Whitford</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/tags/extjs/</link><description>Recent content in ExtJS on Anthony Whitford</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://AnthonyWhitford.com/tags/extjs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Compliance Service</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/compliance-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/compliance-service/</guid><description>Maintaining portfolio compliance is an increasingly challenging problem with regulations constantly changing, investment mandates becoming more sophisticated, and the need to transact at internet speeds. Automation is the only way to scale; an investment manager requires a sophisticated solution that can adapt to the ever changing business rules, and integrate efficiently into the trading workflow. Many investment managers can choose COTS, but sometimes that may not be up to the challenge to address edge cases, or evolve at the pace required by customers.</description></item><item><title>Production Control</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/production-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/production-control/</guid><description>Many enterprises have thousands of automated jobs that run throughout the day and into the night that are critical to business operations. Monitoring these jobs 24x7 and dealing with failures used to require a team.
This project replaced manual job monitoring, alert escalation, and teleconference management with a fully automated solution.
Alarms were received from AutoSys and routed to the appropriate team to investigate and resolve Workflow ensured that alarms were acknowledged and resolved Architected for redundancy; backup controls were in place to ensure uninterrupted monitoring Integrated with xMatters for alert escalation and teleconference management, using REST web services Benefits included:</description></item></channel></rss>