<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Innovation on Anthony Whitford</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/tags/innovation/</link><description>Recent content in Innovation on Anthony Whitford</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://AnthonyWhitford.com/tags/innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enterprise Technical Architecture Program</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/architecture/</guid><description>Why Enterprise Architecture? Organizations of sufficient size and complexity need to organize themselves to make smart decisions, foster innovation, and avoid being overburdened by technical debt.
This program:
Engaged Gartner Consulting to outline a modern Enterprise Architecture framework that focused on coaching and steering Established a Technical Architecture Committee with cross IT representation as a decision-making body that improved management of innovation and technical debt, and communicated standards Documented a Technical Reference Architecture, a living document that included guardrails (Principles, Patterns, and Standards) for teams Created a Center of Excellence to gather feedback from teams and help prioritize evolution Organized guest speakers and Lunch and Learns to raise awareness of industry trends Benefits included:</description></item><item><title>Kozzet</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/kozzet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/kozzet/</guid><description>People love the convenience of mobile ordering at home, but what about when they are away from home? Kozzet adds mobile ordering and chat services to any hospitality provider. It is a great addition to hotels &amp;amp; resorts, golf &amp;amp; country clubs, entertainment venues, and restaurants &amp;amp; cafés.
I founded the company:
Bootstrapped the corporate infrastructure; setup email, web site, phone service, accounting, and CRM Developed a platform using cloud native architecture; created two mobile apps architected for global deployment: one for consumers, and the other for businesses Leveraged Firebase and Google Cloud, and integrated Twilio and Stripe Launched marketing campaigns using social media and print Results included:</description></item></channel></rss>