<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Investment Management on Anthony Whitford</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/tags/investment-management/</link><description>Recent content in Investment Management on Anthony Whitford</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://AnthonyWhitford.com/tags/investment-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Compliance Service</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/compliance-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/compliance-service/</guid><description>Maintaining portfolio compliance is an increasingly challenging problem with regulations constantly changing, investment mandates becoming more sophisticated, and the need to transact at internet speeds. Automation is the only way to scale; an investment manager requires a sophisticated solution that can adapt to the ever changing business rules, and integrate efficiently into the trading workflow. Many investment managers can choose COTS, but sometimes that may not be up to the challenge to address edge cases, or evolve at the pace required by customers.</description></item><item><title>PRISM</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/prism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/prism/</guid><description>Led a team to build Portfolio Risk Information System Management (PRISM), a global investment management platform that connects information, people and technology required to manage money in real time. It covered the full investment process across asset classes, including:
A single view of truth, updated in real time Institutionalized business processes Constituent level benchmark data and security analytics Ability to analyze risk across multiple dimensions Industry leading level of automation for portfolio compliance Integration with trading networks Straight Through Processing, including integration with brokers and custodians via SWIFT and FIX GIPS performance reporting and performance attribution Benefits included:</description></item></channel></rss>