<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dart on Anthony Whitford</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/tags/dart/</link><description>Recent content in Dart on Anthony Whitford</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://AnthonyWhitford.com/tags/dart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Animated Text Kit</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/contributions/animated-text-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/contributions/animated-text-kit/</guid><description>Animated Text Kit is a Flutter package that contains a collection of some cool and awesome text animations:
Colorize Fade Rotate Scale TextLiquidFill Typer Typewriter Wavy I was inspired to contribute to this project after using it to jazz up a splash screen. My contributions include:
fixed bugs and refactored code to make it more efficient and reliable 🚀 increased unit test coverage 📈 managed issues, reviewed code, and released patches 🚧 Recognized for my contributions as a collaborator, I was invited to also be a publisher for the project.</description></item><item><title>Flutter FormBuilder</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/contributions/flutter_form_builder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/contributions/flutter_form_builder/</guid><description>Flutter FormBuilder is an innovative Flutter package that helps creating and managing forms in Flutter. It:
reduces the boilerplate needed to build forms validates fields reacts to changes collects the values for the form I am a collaborator on this project and contribute changes that help make this project better.</description></item><item><title>Kozzet</title><link>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/kozzet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AnthonyWhitford.com/projects/creations/kozzet/</guid><description>People love the convenience of mobile ordering at home, but what about when they are away from home? Kozzet adds mobile ordering and chat services to any hospitality provider. It is a great addition to hotels &amp;amp; resorts, golf &amp;amp; country clubs, entertainment venues, and restaurants &amp;amp; cafés.
I founded the company:
Bootstrapped the corporate infrastructure; setup email, web site, phone service, accounting, and CRM Developed a platform using cloud native architecture; created two mobile apps architected for global deployment: one for consumers, and the other for businesses Leveraged Firebase and Google Cloud, and integrated Twilio and Stripe Launched marketing campaigns using social media and print Results included:</description></item></channel></rss>